There have been many great drivers but only one great passenger.
Even Cowgirls Get the Blues is a comedy, drama,
romance film directed by Gus Van Sant.
A girl born with enormous thumbs in the repressive era of the
1950s learns to turn her quirks into assets.
Sissy Hankshaw, played by Uma Thurman.
Delores Del Ruby, played by Lorraine Bracco.
The Chink, played by Pat Morita.
Miss Adrian, played by Angie Dickinson.
Julian Gitche, played by Keanu Reeves.
The Countess, played by John Hurt.
Even Cowgirls Get the Blues is a 1993 American romantic comedy-drama
western film based on Tom Robbins' 1976 novel of the same title.
The film was written and directed by Gus Van Sant (credited as Gus Van Sant Jr.) and stars an ensemble cast led by Uma
Thurman, Lorraine Bracco, Angie Dickinson, Noriyuki "Pat" Morita, Keanu Reeves, John Hurt, and Rain Phoenix.
Robbins himself narrates.
The soundtrack is sung entirely by k.d.
The film is dedicated to the late River Phoenix.
The film explores themes of transvestism, cowgirl, lgbt, hitchhiking.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.